U.S. National Mediation Board Agreements 5806
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- The Monongahela Connecting Railroad Company Missouri- Illinois Railroad Company (Box 17, Folder 4)
- The Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway Company (Box 17, Folder 5)
- he Atchison, Topeka, and Santa Fe Railway Union Pacific Railroad Company (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Wabash Railroad Company (Box 17, Folder 7)
- St. Louis Missouri Railway Companies (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Consolidated Rail Burlington Northern Inc. Corporation (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Erie Railroad + Besemer and Lake Erie Railroad + The Virginian Railway Companies (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Norfolk Railway Companies (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Lake Erie, Franklin and Clarion Railroad Company (Box 17, Folder 12)
- The Denver and Rio Grande Western Railroad Company (Box 17, Folder 13)
- The Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway Company (Box 17, Folder 14)
- The Delaware, Lackawanna and Western Railroad Company + The Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific Railway Company (Box 17, Folder 15)
- The Pittsburgh and Lake Erie Railroad Company + The Lake Erie and Eastern Railroad Company (Box 18, Folder 1)
- The Pittsburgh and Lake Erie Railroad Company + The Lake Erie and Eastern Railroad (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Pennsylvania Railroad Company (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Peoria and Pekin Union Railway Company (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Pere Marquette Railway Company (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Piedmont and Northern Railway Company (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Pittsburgh and Shawmut Railroad Company (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Penn Central Transportation Company (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Chicago Railway Companies + Pacific Fruit Express Company (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Penn Central Transportation Company (Box 18, Folder 10)
- The Chesapeake and Ohio Railway Company (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Chicago and Eastern Illinois Railway Company (Box 18, Folder 12)
- The Detroit and Mackinac Railway Company + The Detroit Toledo and Ironton Railroad Company (Box 18, Folder 13)
- The Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation (Box 18, Folder 14)
- Chicago Union Station and Chicago West Pullman and Southern Railroad Company (Box 18, Folder 15)
- The Cincinnati Union Terminal Company (Box 18, Folder 16)
- The Colorado and Southern Railway Company (Box 18, Folder 17)
- The Colorado and Wyoming Railway Company (Box 18, Folder 18)
- Columbus and Greenville Railway Company (Box 18, Folder 19)
- Chicago Railway Companies (Box 18, Folder 20)
- Miscellaneous Railroad Companies (Box 18, Folder 21)
- National Carriers Conference Committee (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Chicago and Illinois Midland Railway Company (Box 19, Folder 2)
- The New York Central Railroad Company (Box 19, Folder 3)
- The New York Central Railroad (Box 19, Folder 4)
- National Railway Labor Conference (Box 19, Folder 5)
- St. Louis- San Francisco Railway Company (Box 19, Folder 6)
- St. Louis San Francisco Railway Company (Box 19, Folder 7)
- St. Louis San Francisco Railway Company (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Sacramento Northern Railway (Box 19, Folder 9)
- St. Louis San Francisco Railway Company (Box 19, Folder 10)
- St. Louis- San Francisco Railroad Company (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Pittsburgh, Chartiers, and Youghiogheny Railway Company (Box 19, Folder 12)
- The Portland Terminal Company (Box 19, Folder 13)
- The Pullman Company (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Miscellaneous (Box 19, Folder 15)
- New York Central Railroad (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Penn Central Corporation (Box 20, Folder 2)
- New York Central Railroad (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Norfolk and Western Railway + New York Susquehanna and Western Railroad Company (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Norfolk and Western Railroad Company (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Northern Pacific Railway Company (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Pacific Electric Railway Company + Southern Pacific Transportation Company (Box 20, Folder 7)
- New York Central Railroad Company (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Norfolk and Western Railway Company (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Missouri Pacific Railroad Company (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Northern Pacific Railroad Company (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Pacific Electric Railway Company (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Miscellaneous (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Maine Central Railroad Company (Box 20, Folder 14)
- Maine Central Railroad Company (Box 20, Folder 15)
- New York Railroad Companies (Box 20, Folder 16)
- Louisville and Nashville Railroad Company (Box 20, Folder 17)
- Ogden Union Railway and Depot Company (Box 20, Folder 18)
- Houston Belt and Terminal Railway Company (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Harbor Belt Line Railroad (Box 21, Folder 2)
- 40-hour-week Agreement (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Decisions of the Committee- Article VI Thereof (Box 21, Folder 4)
- New Orleans Public Belt Railroad (Box 21, Folder 5)
- The Newburgh and South Shore Railway Company Brotherhood of Railway Clerks (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Missouri Pacific Lines (Box 21, Folder 7)
- International Great- Northern Ireland Railway (Box 21, Folder 8)
- The Monongahela Railway Company (Box 21, Folder 9)
- The Monongahela Railway Company+ Chattanooga and St. Louis Railway (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Missouri- Kansas- Texas Railroad Company (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Missouri Pacific Railroad Company (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Missouri- Kansas- Texas Railroad Company (Box 21, Folder 13)
- Maine Central Railroad Company (Box 21, Folder 14)
- Michigan Central Railroad+ Midland Continental Railroad (Box 21, Folder 15)
- Gulf Mobile and Ohio Railroad Company (Box 21, Folder 16)
- Miscellaneous, Railroad Companies (Box 21, Folder 17)
- McCloud River Railroad Company+ McKeesport Connecting Railroad Company (Box 21, Folder 18)
- Great Northern Railway Company+ Los Angeles Junction Railway Company (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Lehigh Valley Railroad Company+ The Kansas City Southern Railway Company (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Long Island Railroad Company (Box 22, Folder 3)
- St. Johnsburg and Lake Champlain Railroad Company+ Vermont Northern Railway Company (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Elgin, Joliet and Eastern Railway Company (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Los Angeles Junction Railway Company+ Lehigh and Hudson River Valley Company (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Kentucky and Indiana Terminal Railroad Company (Box 22, Folder 7)
- The Lake Terminal Railroad Company (Box 22, Folder 8)
- The Kansas City Southern Railway Company+ Louisiana and Arkansas Railway Company (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Illinois Central Railroad Company (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Houston Belt and Terminal Railway Company (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Illinois Central Railroad Company (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Grand Trunk Western Railroad Company (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Indiana Harbor Belt Railroad Company (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Kansas City Southern Railway and Indianapolis Union Railway (Box 22, Folder 15)
- International- Great Northern Railroad Company+ Jacksonville Terminal Railway Company (Box 22, Folder 16)
- Kansas, Oklahoma and Gulf Railway Company (Box 22, Folder 17)
- Illinois Central Railroad (Box 22, Folder 18)
- Illinois Central, Indianapolis, and Indiana Railway Companies (Box 22, Folder 19)
- Kansas City Southern Railway Company (Box 22, Folder 20)
- Chicago and Eastern Illinois Railroad (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Fruit Growers Express Company (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Des Moines Union Railway Company (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Denver and Rio Grande Railroad Company (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Erie Lackawanna Railway Company (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Delaware+ Lackawanna+ Rio Grande (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Detroit, Toledo, and Duluth Railroad Companies (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Elgin, Joliet, and Eastern Railway Company (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Erie+ Erie- Lackawanna Railroad Companies (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Florida East Coast Railway Company (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Fort Worth+ Kansas City+ Detroit Railroad Companies (Box 23, Folder 11)
- Clinchfield Railroad Company (Box 23, Folder 12)
- Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific Railroad Company (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Chicago and Illinois Midland Railway Company (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Chicago Railway Companies (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific Railroad Company (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Chicago and Western Indiana Railroad Company (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Chicago Railway Companies (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific Railroad Company (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Chicago, St. Paul, Minneapolis, and Omaha Railway (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Colorado and Southern Railway Company (Box 24, Folder 9)
- Cleveland, Cincinnati, Chicago and St. Louis Railway (Box 24, Folder 10)
- Clinchfield Railroad Company (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Columbus and Greenville Railway Company (Box 24, Folder 12)
- Chicago, St. Paul, Milwaukee+ Chicago Wyoming+ Chicago Union Station Railway Company (Box 24, Folder 13)
- Chesapeake and Ohio Railway Company (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Besemer and Lake Erie Railroad Company (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Birmingham Southern Railway Company (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Boston and Albany Railroad (Box 25, Folder 4)
- The Belt Railway Company of Chicago (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Boston and Albany+ Boston and Maine (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Brooklyn Eastern District Terminal+ Boston Terminal Company (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Buffalo Creek Railroad Company (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Burlington Northern+ Burlington Refrigerator Express Company (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Butte, Anaconda, Pacific Railway Company (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Miscellaneous (Box 25, Folder 11)
- Central of Georgia Railway Company (Box 25, Folder 12)
- The Akron, Canton and Youngstown Railroad Company (Box 25, Folder 13)
- Central of Georgia Railway Company+ Camas Prairie Railroad Company (Box 25, Folder 14)
- The Chesapeake and Ohio Railway Company (Box 25, Folder 15)
- Central of Georgia Railway Company (Box 25, Folder 16)
- Southern Railway Company (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Akron, Canton and Youngstown Railroad Co. (Box 26, Folder 2)
- The Alabama Great Southern Railroad Company (Box 26, Folder 3)
- The Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway Company (Box 26, Folder 4)
- The Ann Arbor Railroad Company (Box 26, Folder 5)
- The Atchison Topeka and Santa Fe Railway Company (Box 26, Folder 6)
- National Railroad Passenger Corporation (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Alton Railroad (Box 26, Folder 8)
- The Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway Corporation (Box 26, Folder 9)
- Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway Company (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Atlantic Coastline Railroad Company (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Baltimore and Ohio Chicago Terminal Railroad Company (Box 26, Folder 12)
- The Belt Railway Company of Chicago (Box 26, Folder 13)
- Bangor and Aroostook Railroad Company (Box 26, Folder 14)
- Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway Company (Box 26, Folder 15)
- Beaver Meade and Englewood Railroad Company (Box 26, Folder 16)
- Miscellaneous (Box 26, Folder 17)
- Tennessee Central Railway Company (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Terminal Railroad Association of St. Louis (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Spokane, Portland and Seattle Railway Company (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Toledo, Peoria and Western Railroad Company (Box 27, Folder 4)
- The Staten Island Rapid Transit Railway Company (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Texas and Pacific Railway Company (Box 27, Folder 6)
- The Virginian Railroad Company (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Union Pacific Railroad Company (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Tremont and Gulf + Texas and New Orleans Railway (Box 27, Folder 9)
- The Virginian Railway Company (Box 27, Folder 10)
- Wabash Railroad Company (Box 27, Folder 11)
- Eastern, Western, and Southeastern Carriers Conference (Box 27, Folder 12)
- The Toledo Terminal Railroad Company (Box 27, Folder 13)
- Trans- Continental Freight Bureau (Box 27, Folder 14)
- Wabash Railway Company (Box 27, Folder 15)
- Virginian Railway Company (Box 27, Folder 16)
- Union Terminal + Union Railroad Companies (Box 27, Folder 17)
- Railroad Co. -W- (Box 27, Folder 18)
- Central of Georgia Railway Company (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Central Railroad N.J. + Central Vermont Railway (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Alton and Southern Railroad + Chicago Eastern Illinois + Southern Railway Company (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Wheeling and Lake Erie Railway Co. + Wichita Terminal Company (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Western Pacific Railroad Company (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Alabama, Tennessee and Northern Railroad Company + Alameda Belt Line (Box 28, Folder 6)
- Railroad Companies -B- (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Boston Railroad Companies (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Railroad Companies -B- (Box 28, Folder 9)
- Railroad Companies -A- (Box 28, Folder 10)
- Butte, Anaconda and pacific Railway Company (Box 28, Folder 11)
- Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway Co. (Box 28, Folder 12)
- Central of Georgia Railway Co. (Box 28, Folder 13)
- Burlington Cos. (Box 28, Folder 14)
- The Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway Company (Box 28, Folder 15)
- The Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway Company (Box 28, Folder 16)
- Miscellaneous B, W (Box 28, Folder 17)
- Center Rapids and Iowa City Railway Company, Camas Prairie Railroad Company (Box 28, Folder 18)
- Southern Pacific Company (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Southern Pacific Company (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Southern Pacific Company (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Southern Pacific Company (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Southern Pacific Company (Box 29, Folder 5)
- Seaboard Coast Line Railroad Company (Box 29, Folder 6)
- Seaboard Coast Line Railroad Company (Box 29, Folder 7)
- Seaboard Coast Line Railroad Company (Box 29, Folder 8)
- Minneapolis St. Paul and Sault Ste. Marie Railroad Company (Box 29, Folder 9)
- Seaboard Air Line Railway Company (Box 29, Folder 10)
- Soo Line Railroad Company (Box 29, Folder 11)
- Savannah Union Station Company, Seaboard Airline Company (Box 29, Folder 12)
- St. Louis- San Francisco Railway Company- St. Louis Southwestern Railway Company (Box 29, Folder 13)
- St. Louis- San Francisco + St. Louis Southwestern (Box 29, Folder 14)
- Union Inland Freight Station + Union Depot Company + Union Pacific Railroad Company (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Union Railroad Company (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Southern Railway Company (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Tennessee Central Railway Company (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Staten Island Companies (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Railway Companies "T" (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Spokane International Railroad Company (Box 30, Folder 7)
- Texas City Terminal Railway Company (Box 30, Folder 8)
- Railway Companies "T", "U" (Box 30, Folder 9)
- Tennessee Central Railway Company (Box 30, Folder 10)
- Southern Pacific Company (Box 30, Folder 11)
- Soo Line Railroad Company (Box 30, Folder 12)
- Seaboard Coast Line Railroad Company (Box 30, Folder 13)
- San Diego and Arizona Eastern Railway Company (Box 30, Folder 14)
- Railway Companies "U" (Box 30, Folder 15)
- Seaboard Coast Line Railroad Company (Box 30, Folder 16)
- Louisiana and Arkansas Railway Company (Box 30, Folder 17)
- Railway Companies "W" (Box 30, Folder 18)
- Norfolk Companies, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- 16 Railway Companies, 1949 (Box 31, Folder 2)
- National Perishable Freight Committee, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- Norfolk Railway Companies, 1967 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Missouri Pacific Railroad Company, 1949-1951 (Box 31, Folder 5)
- Maine Central Railroad Company, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Mucan + Louisville and Nashville Cos., 1961 (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Natchez and Southern Railway Company, 1947 (Box 31, Folder 8)
- Railroad Companies 'L-M' (Box 31, Folder 9)
- Railroad Companies 'J', 1949 (Box 31, Folder 10)
- Railroad Companies 'I', 1949 (Box 31, Folder 11)
- Kansas Companies, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 12)
- Railroad Companies 'L-M', 1955-1967 (Box 31, Folder 13)
- Railroad Companies 'I', 1962-1966 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Railroad Company 'P', 1948-1963 (Box 32, Folder 2)
- St. Louis San Francisco Railway Company, 1964-1977 (Box 32, Folder 3)
- St. Louis Southwestern Railway Company, 1961 (Box 32, Folder 4)
- St. Louis Southwestern Railway Company, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 5)
- Pittsburgh and Lake Erie Railroad Company, 1951 (Box 32, Folder 6)
- St. Louis - San Francisco Railway Company, 1955-1964 (Box 32, Folder 7)
- Railroad Companies 'N', 1975 (Box 32, Folder 8)
- Penn Central Transportation Company, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 9)
- Railroad Companies 'P-R', 1956-1973 (Box 32, Folder 10)
- Railroad Companies 'P', 1969 (Box 32, Folder 11)
- Railroad Companies 'P', 1978 (Box 32, Folder 12)
- Misc. Railroad Companies, 1949 (Box 32, Folder 13)
- New Orleans Public Belt Railroad, 1949 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Illinois Central Railroad Company (Box 33, Folder 2)
- Grand Trunk Western + Gulf Coast Railroad Companies, 1956 (Box 33, Folder 3)
- Gulf.. Railroad Companies, 1960 (Box 33, Folder 4)
- Railroad Companies 'H', 1975 (Box 33, Folder 5)
- Erie Railroad Company, 1946 (Box 33, Folder 6)
- Florida East Coast Railway Company, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 7)
- Florida East Coast Railway Company, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 8)
- Grand Trunk Western Railroad Company, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 9)
- Duluth, South Shore and Atlantic RR Co., 1950 (Box 33, Folder 10)
- Illinois Central Railroad Company, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 11)
- Missouri-Kansas-Texas + Chicago and Midland Company, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 12)
- Elgin, Joliet and Eastern Railway Company + Illinois Central Railroad Company (Box 33, Folder 13)
- Grand Trunk Western Railroad Company, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 14)
- Elgin, Joliet and Eastern Railway Company, 1971 (Box 33, Folder 15)
- The Western Pacific Railroad Company, 1952 (Box 33, Folder 16)
- St. Louis-San Francisco + St. Louis Southwestern Railway Company, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 17)
- Misc. Railway Companies, 1957 (Box 33, Folder 18)
- Southern Pacific, 1945-1955 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Texas and Pacific + Tennessee Central Railway Companies, 1957-1972 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- Illinois Central System + Seaboard Air Line Railroad Company + Great Northern Railway, 1954-1978 (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Union Pacific Railroad Company + Illinois Central System, 1932-1937 (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Union Terminal + International + Great Northern Railroad Company, 1939-1941 (Box 34, Folder 5)
- Gulf, Mobile and Ohio Railroad Company + Houston Belt Terminal + Grand Trunk Western Railroad Company, 1953-1970 (Box 34, Folder 6)
- Southern Pacific, 1944-1963 (Box 34, Folder 7)
- Illinois Terminal + Western Pacific Railroad Companies, 1943-1973 (Box 34, Folder 8)
- The Chesapeake and Ohio Railway Company, 1982 (Box 34, Folder 9)
- The Washington Terminal Company, 1972 (Box 34, Folder 10)
- N.O. Public Belt Railroad, 1981 (Box 34, Folder 11)
- Railway Companies "N", 1949 (Box 34, Folder 12)
- Vacation Agreement between Certain Eastern, Western and Southeastern Carriers, 1941 (Box 34, Folder 13)
- Southeastern Demurrage and Storage Bureau, 1943-1963 (Box 34, Folder 14)
- The Washington Terminal Company, 1972 (Box 34, Folder 15)
- Burlington Northern, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 16)
- Railroad Companies "S", 1942-1953 (Box 35, Folder 1)
- Railroad Companies "P-S', 1942-1956 (Box 35, Folder 2)
- The Pennsylvania Railroad Company, 1935-1943 (Box 35, Folder 3)
- Illinois Central Gulf Railroad (Box 35, Folder 4)
- Pullman Company + Railway Express Agency, 1937-1949 (Box 35, Folder 5)
- Railway Companies "S", 1946-1972 (Box 35, Folder 6)
- Railway Companies "P-S", 1941-1968 (Box 35, Folder 7)
- Railroad Companies "S", 1968-1971 (Box 35, Folder 8)
- Minneapolis, St. Paul and Sault Marie Railroad Company, 1934-1944 (Box 35, Folder 9)
- The National Railroad Passenger Corporation, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 10)
- Railway Companies "C", 1953-1968 (Box 36, Folder 1)
- Railway Companies "B-C", 1942-1964 (Box 36, Folder 2)
- Burlington North + Duluth Railroad Companies, 1940-1968 (Box 36, Folder 3)
- Railway Companies, Chicago, Central of Georgia, 1926-1958 (Box 36, Folder 4)
- Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific Railway Company + The Central Railroad Co., 1927-1963 (Box 36, Folder 5)
- Railroad Companies "C", 1946-1951 (Box 36, Folder 6)
- The Chesapeake and Ohio Railway Company, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 7)
- Southern Pacific Company, 1965 (Box 36, Folder 8)
- Spokane Railroad Companies, 1942-1961 (Box 36, Folder 9)
- Railroad Companies "S-T", 1945-1973 (Box 36, Folder 10)
- Lake Terminal Railroad Company, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 11)
- The Pennsylvania Railroad + The Chesapeake and Ohio Railway Company, 1946-1947 (Box 37, Folder 1)
- Burlington Northern Inc., 1972 (Box 37, Folder 2)
- The Long Island Railroad (Box 37, Folder 3)
- Railroad Companies 'L-M', 1951-1959 (Box 37, Folder 4)
- Railway Companies 'N', 1943-1949 (Box 37, Folder 5)
- New York Railroad Companies, 1944-1957 (Box 37, Folder 6)
- Chesapeake and Ohio Railway Company + Missouri Pacific Lines, 1927-1953 (Box 37, Folder 7)
- Chesapeake and Ohio Railway + Norfolk Southern Railway Company, 1945-1962 (Box 37, Folder 8)
- Northern Pacific Railway Company + Pennsylvania Railroad Company, 1957-1965 (Box 37, Folder 9)
- Belt Railway Company, 1964 (Box 37, Folder 10)
- Railroad Companies 'I-L', 1945-1973 (Box 37, Folder 11)
- Chicago.. Railway Companies, 1952-1967 (Box 38, Folder 1)
- Railroad Companies 'C' (Central), 1947-1959 (Box 38, Folder 2)
- The Chesapeake and Ohio Railway Company, 1931-1956 (Box 38, Folder 3)
- Atlanta and Saint Andrews Bay Railways Company, 1976 (Box 38, Folder 4)
- Denver and Rio Grande Western Railroad Company, 1947-1968 (Box 38, Folder 5)
- Chicago Railway Companies, 1940-1962 (Box 38, Folder 6)
- Railroad Companies 'B-C', 1944-1963 (Box 38, Folder 7)
- Railway Companies A-C, 1946-1967 (Box 38, Folder 8)
- Railway Companies 'A', 1977 (Box 38, Folder 9)
- Railway Companies A-C, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 10)
- Bessemer and Lak Erie Railroad Company + The Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway Company, 1958-1970 (Box 38, Folder 11)
- Chicago.. Railway Companies, 1946-1955 (Box 39, Folder 1)
- Railway Companies C-D, 1936-1949 (Box 39, Folder 2)
- Railway Companies 'D', 1928-1942 (Box 39, Folder 3)
- Chicago Railway Companies, 1939-1979 (Box 39, Folder 4)
- Railway Companies 'C', 1955-1961 (Box 39, Folder 5)
- Railway Companies, Larger Books, 1932-1979 (Box 39, Folder 6)
- DM and IR Railway Company (Box 39, Folder 7)
- Railway Companies 'C-D', 1945-1952 (Box 39, Folder 8)
- Denver and Rio - Grande Western Railroad Company, 1941 (Box 39, Folder 9)
- Florida East Coast Railway, 1946-1948 (Box 39, Folder 10)
- Chicago Railway Companies, 1926 (Box 39, Folder 11)
- Railway Companies 'F', 1943-1962 (Box 39, Folder 12)
- Educational Great Northern Railroad + Illinois Terminal Railroad Company, 1944 (Box 40, Folder 1)
- Railway Companies 'G', 1953-1968 (Box 40, Folder 2)
- Railway Companies 'E', 1942-1945 (Box 40, Folder 3)
- Railways Companies 'D', 1940-1957 (Box 40, Folder 4)
- Railway Companies 'N', 1936-1949 (Box 40, Folder 5)
- Northern Pacific Railway Company, 1943-1968 (Box 40, Folder 6)
- Great Northern Railway Company, 1940-1947 (Box 40, Folder 7)
- Fort Worth and Denver Railway Company, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 8)
- Norfolk and Western Railway Company, 1959-1963 (Box 40, Folder 9)
- New York Central Railroad Company, 1945-1952 (Box 40, Folder 10)
- Missouri Pacific Railroad Company, 1947-1953 (Box 40, Folder 11)
- Railway Companies 'M', 1940-1962 (Box 40, Folder 12)
- Railway Companies 'A', 1929 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- The Long Island Railroad Company, 1977-1978 (Box 41, Folder 2)
- New York Railway Companies + Texas Mexican Railway Company, 1958-1972 (Box 41, Folder 3)
- Railway Companies 'A', 1956-1958 (Box 41, Folder 4)
- New York Railway Companies, 1944-1950 (Box 41, Folder 5)
- Railway Companies 'A', 1942-1949 (Box 41, Folder 6)
- New York Railway Companies, 1942-1945 (Box 41, Folder 7)
- Union Pacific Railroad Company, 1945-1958 (Box 41, Folder 8)
- New York Central Railroad, 1928-1943 (Box 41, Folder 9)
- Louisville and Nashville Railroad Company, 1938-1966 (Box 41, Folder 10)
- Agreement DM and IR Railway (Box 41, Folder 11)
- Kentucky and Indiana Terminal Railroad Company, 1944 (Box 41, Folder 12)
- Cincinnati + Chicago Railway Companies, 1940-1948 (Box 41, Folder 13)
- Illinois Central Gulf Railroad, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 14)
- Agreement DM and IR Railway Company, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 1)
- Agreement DM and IR Railway Company, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 2)
- Agreement DM and IR Railway Company, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 3)
- Union Pacific Railroad + The Virginian Railway Company, 1948-1973 (Box 42, Folder 4)